Verle G. Kaiser Papers 1932-1982
Washington State University Libraries: Manuscripts, Archives, and Special Collections (MASC)
- International Projects, Series 7
  - Iran, 7.3
    - Karkheh: Notes from Reconnaissance Survey, 1975; 6 items. (Box 13, Folder 808)
      - Survey and Development, 1971-1975; 9 items. (Box 13, Folder 810)
    - Karkheh River Basin: Development Master Plan, 1971; 1 item. (Box 13, Folder 812)
    - KDS Irrigation Clinic and Training Course Temporary Field Farm, Haft Tapeh, 1961; 1 item. (Box 14, Folder 813)
    - Khuzestan Development Service, 1963; 4 items. (Box 14, Folder 814)
      - Fertilizer Program, 1957-1962; 1 item. (Box 14, Folder 815)
      - Water and Power Authority, Dez Pilot Irrigation Project: Agricultural Production Estimates, 1963; 1 item. (Box 14, Folder 816)
      - Water and Power Authority, Dez Pilot Irrigation Project: Agricultural Production Estimates, undated; 3 items. (Box 14, Folder 817)
    - Leo Anderson's Material on Iran Talk, 1977; 10 items. (Box 14, Folder 818)
    - Maps of Iran, undated; 3 items. (Box 14, Folder 819)
    - Material on David E. Lilienthal and Karkheh Basin, 1967-1969; 1 item. (Box 14, Folder 820)
    - Materials on PSM, 1975-1976; 14 items. (Box 14, Folder 821)
    - Materials Put Together for Village Agents, Dez Project, 1963; 5 items. (Box 14, Folder 822)
    - Materials To Complete, 1976; 3 items. (Box 14, Folder 823)
    - Memo To Agricultural Staff and Glossary of Agricultural Terms, 1962; 2 items. (Box 14, Folder 824)
    - Ministry of Agriculture Activities, Travel Report, 1975; 2 items. (Box 14, Folder 825)
      - Annual Report, 1973-1975; 1 item. (Box 14, Folder 826)
    - Mixed Materials, undated; 15 items. (Box 14, Folder 827)
    - NARP, 1975; 6 items. (Box 14, Folder 828)
    - Natural Resources in Iran, 1967; 1 item. (Box 14, Folder 829)
    - Natural Resources in Iran, 1967-1968; 1 item. (Box 14, Folder 830)
    - Natural Resources in Iran, 1967-1968; 1 item. (Box 14, Folder 831)
    - Notes from Reconnaissance Survey, Upper Karkheh River Basin, undated; 2 items. (Box 14, Folder 832)
    - Notes: Agricultural-Vocational Programs, Esfahan, 1976; 8 items. (Box 14, Folder 833)
    - Partial List of References Applicable to Conditions in Iran, undated; 1 item. (Box 14, Folder 834)
    - Photographs of Verle G. Kaiser in Iran, undated; 19 items. (Box 14, Folder 835)
    - Preliminary Irrigation Reconnaissance Survey of the Provinces of Kurdestan and Kermanshah, 1966; 1 item. (Box 14, Folder 836)
    - Preparing Seed Bed and Planting Crops in Mechanized Agriculture, undated; 3 items. (Box 14, Folder 837)
    - Provinces in Iran: Crop Production in Dez Pilot Area, Session Eight, undated; 2 items. (Box 14, Folder 838)
    - Public Sector Management, Session One, undated; 5 items. (Box 14, Folder 839)
      - Project, Phase II, 1975-1977; 27 items. (Box 14, Folder 840)
      - Project, Phase II, 1977; 3 items. (Box 14, Folder 841)
    - Report on Crop Studies and Testing Programs, Haft Tapeh, 1962-1963; 1 item. (Box 14, Folder 842)
    - Report on Berseen Clover, Dez Pilot Area, 1962; 1 item. (Box 14, Folder 843)
    - Short-Term Management Recommendations, 1976; 1 item. (Box 14, Folder 844)
    - Status of Dez Irrigation Project: Briefing Papers, IBRD Representative, 1961; 4 items. (Box 14, Folder 845)
    - Story of the Bakhtiari, Historical Notes, undated; 1 item. (Box 14, Folder 846)
    - Summary of Field Trials and Investigations, Dez Pilot Irrigation Project, Chapters I and II, 1963; 1 item. (Box 14, Folder 847)
    - Summary of Field Trials and Investigations, Dez Pilot Irrigation Project, Chapters III-VIII, 1963; 1 item. (Box 14, Folder 848)
    - Summary Report: Field Crop Testing Studies, Upper Khuzestan Plains, 1958-1960; 1 item. (Box 14, Folder 849)
      - Field Trials and Investigations, DPIP, 1964; 1 item. (Box 14, Folder 851)
    - Teaching Outline, Peace Corps, 1964-1974; 19 items. (Box 14, Folder 852)
    - Teheran Journal, Volume 23, 1976; 1 item. (Box 14, Folder 853)
    - The Bakhtiaris: Notes from an 800-km Trip, 1961; 1 item. (Box 14, Folder 854)
    - The Unified Development of the Khuzestan Region, 1959; 1 item. (Box 14, Folder 855)
  - Nicaragua, 7.4
    - Area To Be Covered: Three-Year Project, Proposed Ten-Year Program for Tax-Improvement and Natural Resources Inventory in Nicaragua, 1967; 1 item. (Box 14, Folder 856)
    - Background and History of Meteorological Activity in Nicaragua, 1967; 1 item. (Box 14, Folder 857)
    - Catastro Inventory of Natural Resources: Practical Interpretation for the Use of Soil Maps, 1971; 1 item. (Box 14, Folder 858)
      - 1968-1969, 1 item. (Box 15, Folder 859)
      - Work Plan and Program Proposal, undated; 1 item. (Box 15, Folder 860)
    - Consultant's Report, Reconnaissance Ecological Survey in Western Nicaragua, 1969; 1 item. (Box 15, Folder 861)
    - Draft Material, Nicaraguan Project, undated; 33 items. (Box 15, Folder 862)
    - Fiscal Cadaster, 1967; 1 item. (Box 15, Folder 863)
    - Geology and Geomorphology, 1967; 1 item. (Box 15, Folder 864)
    - Hydrology and Well-Drilling Section, undated; 1 item. (Box 15, Folder 865)
    - Natural Resources Inventory and Tax Improvement Project: Work Plan, 1967; 1 item. (Box 15, Folder 866)
    - Report to Development and Resources Corporation: Soil Survey, undated; 1 item. (Box 15, Folder 867)
    - Soil and Land Use Survey Report, undated; 3 items. (Box 15, Folder 868-70)
    - Soil and Vegetation Surveys, 1971; 1 item. (Box 15, Folder 871)
    - Soil Survey, Classification and History of Western Nicaragua, undated; 2 items. (Box 15, Folder 872-3)
    - Surface Water Hydrology and Ground Water Hydrology, 1967; 16 items. (Box 15, Folder 874)
    - Tax Improvement and Natural Resources Inventory Project, Work Plan, 1967; 1 item. (Box 15, Folder 875)
    - Verle G. Kaiser's Plans for a Short Trip To Nicaragua, 1969; 6 items. (Box 15, Folder 876)
- Personal Interests And Activities, Series 8
  - "A Look Abroad: The Effect of Foreign Travel on Domestic Outdoor Recreation and a Brief Survey of Outdoor Recreation in Six Countries", 1962; 1 item. (Box 15, Folder 877)
  - A 1975 View of an 1811 Trip with David Thompson From the Snake River to Spokane House, 2 items. (Box 15, Folder 878)
  - AAVCG Member Monthly Publication, "Eternal Vigilance is the Price of Liberty", 1982; 1 item. (Box 15, Folder 897)
  - Annual Inland Empire Chapter SCSA Spring Meeting, 1981; 18 items. (Box 15, Folder 880)
  - "Bodaceous Mountain", undated; 1 item. (Box 15, Folder 881)
  - "Bodaceous Mounatin" and "Lost Hunters", undated; 2 items. (Box 15, Folder 882)
  - Booklet on "Communist Infiltration in the United States", 1946; 1 item. (Box 15, Folder 883)
  - Brooks-Hensley-Creager Architects, undated; 1 item. (Box 15, Folder 884)
  - "Camp Visitors", undated; 1 item. (Box 15, Folder 885)
  - "Camp Visitors" and "Club Bodaceous", undated; 2 items. (Box 15, Folder 886)
  - Carbon Copy of "Hunters and Sadface Creek", undated; 2 items. (Box 15, Folder 887)
  - Carbon copy of "Little Joe Little", undated; 2 items. (Box 15, Folder 888)
  - Carbon copy of "Sheesh 'K Bob", undated; 1 item. (Box 15, Folder 889)
  - "Club Bodaceous", undated; 1 item. (Box 15, Folder 890)
  - Commonly Used Rough Draft Maps, undated; 8 items. (Box 15, Folder 891)
  - Concerns and Philosophy as State Agronomist, undated; 52 items. (Box 15, Folder 892)
  - Concerns and Philosophy as State Agronomist, undated; 40 items. (Box 15, Folder 893)
  - Correspondence: "Conservation Cropping Systems for the Palouse", undated; 6 items. (Box 15, Folder 894)
  - Development and Resources Corporation, 1947-1979; 3 items. (Box 15, Folder 895)
  - Development and Resources Corporation, 1974-1975; 10 items. (Box 15, Folder 896)
  - Development and Resources Corporation. Disbursement, 1976; 5 items. (Box 15, Folder 897)
  - Environmental Guild of Spokane, 1975-1978; 14 items. (Box 15, Folder 898)
  - Environmental Guild of Spokane, 1976; 1 item. (Box 15, Folder 899)
  - Equipment Needs: Requisitions, Notes, Data on Tillage, 1961; 44 items. (Box 15, Folder 900)
  - Equipment Needs: Requisitions, Notes, Data on Tillage, 1961; 36 items. (Box 15, Folder 901)
  - Expense Accounts, 1975-1976; 62 items. (Box 15, Folder 902)
  - Fiscal Records, 1960-1971; 78 items. (Box 15, Folder 903)
  - Forty-Ninth Meeting of the Northwest Scientific Association, EWSC, 1976; 1 item. (Box 15, Folder 904)
  - "From the Snake River to Spokane House with David Thompson in 1811: A Retrospective View", undated; 1 item. (Box 15, Folder 905)
  - Fundamentals of Elementary Flight Maneuvers, Civil Aeronautics Bulletin, 1943; 1 item. (Box 15, Folder 906)
  - "Grain Recropping, a Conservation Practice for Grainlands in Eastern Washington and Northern Idaho", 1963; 2 items. (Box 15, Folder 907-908)
  - Historical Land Use and Erosion in the Palouse: A Reappraisal, 1961; 1 item. (Box 15, Folder 909)
  - "Hunter's Stew", undated; 1 item. (Box 15, Folder 910)
  - "Hunting in the United States", 1962; 1 item. (Box 15, Folder 911)
  - Inland Empire Chapter of Soil Conservation Society of America and Journals, 1981; 10 items. (Box 16, Folder 912)
  - Itineraries and Prices for Soil Conservation of America, 1981; 33 items. (Box 16, Folder 913)
  - "Know Your Soils," Verle G. Kaiser addresses the Moscow Chamber of Commerce, 1947; 1 item. (Box 16, Folder 914)
  - Letter from Work Unit Conservationist to each Supervisor, undated; 2 items. (Box 16, Folder 915)
  - Letters to Wife and Mother, 1960-1961; 2 items. (Box 16, Folder 916)
  - Liberty School District, Spangle, 1979; 23 items. (Box 16, Folder 917)
    - Board Meetings, 1980; 22 items. (Box 16, Folder 918)
  - "Little Joe Little", undated; 1 item. (Box 16, Folder 919)
  - "Lost Hunters", undated; 6 items. (Box 16, Folder 920)
  - Manuscript Clearance and Copy of "Grain Recropping, A Conservation Practice for Grainlands in Eastern Washington and Northern Idaho", 1962; 3 items. (Box 16, Folder 921)
  - Map of the Western Portion of Washington, undated; 1 item. (Box 16, Folder 922)
  - Material for SCSA Tours, undated; 5 items. (Box 16, Folder 923)
  - Materials Gathered At Soil Conservation Convention, Spokane, 1981; 14 items. (Box 16, Folder 924)
  - Materials Presented to Fertilizer Dealers' Workshop, 1965; 1 item. (Box 16, Folder 925)
  - Miscellaneous Maps, undated; 8 items. (Box 16, Folder 926)
    - National Forest Maps, undated; 13 items. (Box 16, Folder 927)
    - Rough Draft Maps, undated; 9 items. (Box 16, Folder 928)
  - Nez Perce Maps, undated; 6 items. (Box 16, Folder 929)
  - "North to Nakolot Lodge," Canada, 1965; 1 item. (Box 16, Folder 930)
  - "October Fever," Elk Hunting, undated; 1 item. (Box 16, Folder 931)
  - One Thousand Mile Club, undated; 12 items. (Box 16, Folder 932)
  - OPDA USDA Newsletter, undated; 1 item. (Box 16, Folder 933)
  - "Preserve Our Paradise" Association, Spokane, 1976; 6 items. (Box 16, Folder 934)
  - Published Articles and Interviews, 1961-1967; 27 items. (Box 16, Folder 935)
  - Published Articles and Interviews, 1936-1965; 6 items. (Box 16, Folder 936)
  - "Quesnell Trip", 1969; 1 item. (Box 16, Folder 937)
  - Recommendations on Soil Conservation in the Palouse, 1969; 1 item. (Box 16, Folder 938)
  - Reports and Writings on Palouse Problems, 1961-1967; 8 items. (Box 16, Folder 939)
  - Residue Calculation for Amounts of Residue After Stubble Mulching Operations, undated; 1 item. (Box 16, Folder 940)
  - "Sadface Creek", undated; 1 item. (Box 16, Folder 941)
  - Scripts for Slide Talks:
    - undated, 7 items. (Box 16, Folder 942)
    - prior to 1950, undated, 8 items. (Box 16, Folder 943)
    - 1950-1955, 13 items. (Box 16, Folder 944)
    - 1955-1960, 7 items. (Box 16, Folder 945)
    - 1955-1960, 6 items. (Box 16, Folder 946)
    - 1960-1964, 10 items. (Box 16, Folder 947)
    - 1965, 12 items. (Box 16, Folder 948)
    - 1965, 6 items. (Box 16, Folder 949)
    - 1966, 4 items. (Box 16, Folder 950)
    - 1975, 1 item. (Box 17, Folder 951)
  - SCSA Convention Technical Tours Committee, 1981; 6 items. (Box 17, Folder 952)
  - SCSA Convention Technical Tours Committee, 1980; 12 items. (Box 17, Folder 953)
  - "Sheesh 'K Bob", undated; 1 item. (Box 17, Folder 954)
  - Slide Sequence Records for Talks, 1944-1950; 2 items. (Box 17, Folder 955)
    - Slide Talk on the Importance of Conservation, Davenport-Rearden Conservation District, 1973; 2 items. (Box 17, Folder 956)
  - Soil Conservation Society of America, Roster of Officers and Committees, 1979-1981; 6 items. (Box 17, Folder 957)
    - Convention, Spokane, 1981; 4 items. (Box 17, Folder 958)
    - Convention, Spokane, 1981; 6 items. (Box 17, Folder 959)
    - Convention, Spokane, 1981; 6 items. (Box 17, Folder 960)
  - Soil Erosion and Wheat Yields in Whitman County, 1967; 1 item. (Box 17, Folder 961)
  - Soil Erosion and Wheat Yields in Whitman County, 1967; 2 items. (Box 17, Folder 962)
  - Soils of the Western United States, 1964; 1 item. (Box 17, Folder 963)
  - Speeches, 1947-1951; 23 items. (Box 17, Folder 964)
  - The Aquatron Manual, 1968; 2 items. (Box 17, Folder 965)
  - The Captain Armstrong Story, undated; 1 item. (Box 17, Folder 966)
  - The Coffee Shop: Menu from Hotel Simon Fraser, undated; 1 item. (Box 17, Folder 967)
  - The Environmental Guild of Spokane, 1978; 1 item. (Box 17, Folder 968)
  - The Future of the Palouse, 1952; 1 item. (Box 17, Folder 969)
  - The Institute of Cultural Affairs, 1979; 1 item. (Box 17, Folder 970)
  - The Wilderness Society Newsletter, 1966; 1 item. (Box 17, Folder 971)
  - "Tillage and Soil Organic Matter", 1959; 1 item. (Box 17, Folder 972)
  - Tillage and the Douglas County Grain Farmer, undated; 1 item. (Box 17, Folder 973)
  - Travel: Arizona, 1979-1980; 25 items. (Box 17, Folder 974)
    - Souvenirs, undated; 16 items. (Box 17, Folder 975)
    - Souvenirs, undated; 18 items. (Box 17, Folder 976)
  - Twenty-Four Better Ways to Communicate, undated; 1 item. (Box 17, Folder 977)
  - Unpublished Articles:
    - 1978, 1 item. (Box 17, Folder 978)
    - Northwest Science Papers, 1945-1967; 11 items. (Box 17, Folder 979)
    - Technical Reports, 1938-1960; 10 items. (Box 17, Folder 980)
    - 1938-1960, 13 items. (Box 17, Folder 981)
    - 1960-1965, 12 items. (Box 17, Folder 982)
    - 1960-1965, 18 items. (Box 17, Folder 983)
    - 1966-1969, 9 items. (Box 17, Folder 984)
    - 1969-1972, 17 items. (Box 17, Folder 985)
  - White River National Forest, Colorado, map, 1975; 2 items. (Box 17, Folder 986)
- Pacific Northwest, Series 9
  - A Structural Program for Runoff Control is Needed on Grain Lands of Pacific Northwest, undated; 1 item. (Box 17, Folder 987)
  - Agricultural Conservation Program, Union County, Oregon, 1955; 1 item. (Box 17, Folder 988)
  - Air Flight Maps: Lake Louise and Columbia River, 1960; 3 items. (Box 17, Folder 989)
  - Air Photo Tracings Used to Build Map of Trapper Basin, 1976; 12 items. (Box 17, Folder 990)
  - "Alfalfa to Replace Sweetclover....", 1960; 1 item. (Box 17, Folder 991)
  - An Airphoto Atlas of the Rural United States: The Far West, undated; 1 item. (Box 17, Folder 992)
  - An Early Elk Hunting Experience in the Bovill Country, 1962; 2 items. (Box 17, Folder 993)
  - Benchmark Soils of Washington, 1965; 1 item. (Box 17, Folder 994)
  - Journal Record, Palouse SCS Farmers, undated; 1 item. (Box 17, Folder 994.5)
  - Journal Record, Palouse SCS Farmers, undated; 1 item. (Box 17, Folder 994.6)
  - Capability Units for Non-irrigated Land Uses: Northern Idaho and Eastern Washington, 1966; 1 item. (Box 17, Folder 995)
  - Chart Criteria for Determining Land Capability Class for Soils of Eastern Washington, undated; 1 item. (Box 17, Folder 996)
  - Clearwater National Forrest Maps, undated; 8 items. (Box 17, Folder 997)
  - Cloudy--Tillage--Horning, undated; 2 items. (Box 17, Folder 998)
  - Columbia: North Pacific Drainage Basin, 1965; 1 item. (Box 17, Folder 999)
  - Columbia Plateau Resources Council:
    - undated, 1 item. (Box 17, Folder 1000)
    - undated, 1 item. (Box 17, Folder 1001)
    - 1965-1967, 46 items. (Box 17, Folder 1002)
    - 1966-1967, 16 items. (Box 17, Folder 1003)
    - 1967, 6 items. (Box 17, Folder 1004)
    - Committee No. Six Reports, 1965-1967; 38 items. (Box 17, Folder 1005)
    - Committee No. Six Reports, 1965; 19 items. (Box 17, Folder 1006)
    - General Information, 1966; 6 items. (Box 17, Folder 1007)
    - General Information and Correspondence, 1967; 31 items. (Box 17, Folder 1008)
    - General Information and Correspondence, 1966-1967; 30 items. (Box 17, Folder 1009)
    - Membership Lists, 1966-1968; 53 items. (Box 17, Folder 1010)
    - Minutes of Meetings, 1966-1968; 53 items. (Box 17, Folder 1011)
    - Minutes of Meetings, Executive Committee Board, 1966; 12 items. (Box 17, Folder 1011)
    - Minutes of Meetings, Executive Committee Board, 1967; 4 items. (Box 17, Folder 1012)
    - Minutes of Meetings, Executive Committee Board, 1967; 11 items. (Box 17, Folder 1013)
    - Minutes of Meetings, Executive Committee Board, 1968-1969; 26 items. (Box 17, Folder 1014)
    - Newsletter, 1966-1968; 40 items. (Box 17, Folder 1015)
    - Newsletter, 1966-1968; 14 items. (Box 18, Folder 1016)
    - Newsletter, 1966-1968; 12 items. (Box 18, Folder 1017)
    - Third Annual Meeting, Spokane, 1967; 1 item. (Box 18, Folder 1018)
  - Columbia River Basin Area Agricultural Program Summary Report, 1954; 1 item. (Box 18, Folder 1019)
  - Columbia River Water Congress, 1966; 1 item. (Box 18, Folder 1020)
    - Wenatchee, 1966; 1 item. (Box 18, Folder 1021)
  - Complete Set of Columbia Plateau Council Newsletters, 1966-1967; 27 items. (Box 18, Folder 1022)
  - Complete Set of Columbia Plateau Council Newsletters, 1966-1968; 10 items. (Box 18, Folder 1023)
  - "Conservation Crop Rotations in the Pacific Northwest", 1957; 1 item. (Box 18, Folder 1024)
  - Conservation Practices and Special Problems, Whitman County and LaCrosse, Washington, 1951-1952; 15 items. (Box 18, Folder 1025)
  - Conservation of Wheat Lands of the Pacific Northwest, 1944; 1 item. (Box 18, Folder 1027)
  - Contour Strip Cropping, 1948; 1 item. (Box 18, Folder 1028)
  - Counties with Severe Wind and Water Erosion Problems, Idaho, Washington and Oregon, 1971-1972; 2 items. (Box 18, Folder 1029)
  - "Damage to Oregon Farms and Ranches by the Recent Floods, 1965; 1 item. (Box 18, Folder 1030)
  - Davenport-Rearden, Southwest Spokane and Sprague-Harrington Soil Conservation Districts, 1951; 16 items. (Box 18, Folder 1031)
  - Description of the Climate, Elevation, Topography, Vegetation, Soils, Water Sources and Type of Agriculture of Cassia, Power, and Oneida Counties, Washington, undated; 1 item. (Box 18, Folder 1032)
  - Description of Lost River Valleys and Mountains, Challis and Salmon, undated; 1 item. (Box 18, Folder 1033)
  - Description of the Northern Rockey Mountain Valleys, undated; 2 items. (Box 18, Folder 1034)
  - Description KL#!e Palouse-Nez Perce Prairies and the Snake River Plains, undated; 2 items. (Box 18, Folder 1035)
  - Description of the Upper Snake River Lava Plains and Hills, and the Great Salt Lake Area of Idaho, undated; 2 items. (Box 18, Folder 1036)
  - Description of the Pacific Northwest Farming Area, 1953; 1 item. (Box 18, Folder 1037)
  - Development and Resources Corporation, undated; 1 item. (Box 18, Folder 1038)
  - Dryland Conservation Farming Guide: Lower Columbia Basin Dryland Farming Area, 1957; 1 item. (Box 18, Folder 1039)
  - Early Roads and Trails, by C.S. Kingston, undated; 6 items. (Box 18, Folder 1040)
  - Early Roads and Trails, by C.S. Kingston, undated; 8 items. (Box 18, Folder 1041)
  - Eastern Washington Grasses and Legumes for Conservation Use in Semiarid Wheat Fallow Areas, 1967; 1 item. (Box 18, Folder 1042)
  - Effect of Conservation Practices on Soil and Water Losses, on Maintenance of soil organic matter, and on Yield and Grain Quality, 1953; 1 item. (Box 18, Folder 1043)
  - Effect of Nitrogen Fertilizer on Wheat Yields, LaCrosse and Walla Walla, Washington, undated; 2 items. (Box 18, Folder 1044)
  - Environmental Conservation Problems, undated; 4 items. (Box 18, Folder 1045)
  - Extra Copies, North Idaho National Forest Maps, undated; 23 items. (Box 18, Folder 1046)
  - Farm Planners Engineering Handbook: Range Management in the Pacific Northwest, undated; 1 item. (Box 18, Folder 1046)
  - Flathead Lake, Montana, undated; 1 item. (Box 18, Folder 1047)
  - Program for International Visitors, Multiregional Development, Spokane, Friday, October 27, 1978; 1 item. (Box 18, Folder 1048)
  - Generalized Water Erosion Map: Columbia Plateau Area of Idaho, Oregon, and Washington, 1967; 1 item. (Box 18, Folder 1049)
  - Geology, Groundwater and Water Quality, Southern Spokane County, Washington, 1975; 1 item. (Box 18, Folder 1050)
  - "How I Think ACP Can Achieve Maximum Effectiveness," Verle Kaiser, undated; 1 item. (Box 18, Folder 1051)
  - Idaho Annual Report, 1961; 1 item. (Box 18, Folder 1052)
  - Idaho Map of Woodlands, Farm Growing Seasons, Fallow Irrigated and Rangelands, undated; 1 item. (Box 18, Folder 1053)
  - Idaho's Mining History, undated; 1 item. (Box 18, Folder 1054)
  - Idaho Technical Committee Minutes, Tri-State Environmental and Conservation Program, Boise, 1970; 2 items. (Box 18, Folder 1055)
  - Information Bulletin: Public Hearing on Proposed Water Quality Standards, Columbia River, 1966; 1 item. (Box 18, Folder 1056)
  - Joint Utah-Idaho Conservation Dryland Farming Guide, 1955; 1 item. (Box 18, Folder 1057)
  - Kamiah Area, 1962; 3 items. (Box 18, Folder 1058)
  - Kaniksu National Forest, eastern Half, Idaho, Montana, Washington, 1941; 3 items. (Box 18, Folder 1059)
  - Land Resources Committee, General Correspondence and Reports, 1966-1967; 38 items. (Box 18, Folder 1060)
  - Land Survey Calculations for Spokane Property, Verle Kaiser, undated; 60 items. (Box 18, Folder 1061)
  - Land Survey: Legal Descriptions, 1974; 15 items. (Box 18, Folder 1062)
  - Legends of the Nez Perce, by Tom Beall, undated; 1 item. (Box 18, Folder 1063)
  - Major Land Resource Area Maps, National and Regional, 1963; 6 items. (Box 18, Folder 1064)
  - Map for Land Resources Area in Idaho, 1963; 1 item. (Box 18, Folder 1065)
  - Map of Spokane and Surrounding Area, 1952; 1 item. (Box 18, Folder 1066)
  - Map of Oregon and Washington, undated; 1 item. (Box 18, Folder 1067)
  - Maps for Sample Farms, undated; 66 items. (Box 18, Folder 1068)
  - Map of Coeur d'Alene Indian Reservation, Nez Perce Indian Reservation, undated; 2 items. (Box 18, Folder 1069)
  - Meeting of Group Four, Columbia Plateau Resources Council, Seattle, Washington, 1966; 1 item. (Box 18, Folder 1070)
  - Mt. St. Helens Eruption, 1980; 4 items. (Box 18, Folder 1071)
  - Nez Perce National Forrest, Idaho, Map, 1959; 1 item. (Box 18, Folder 1072)
  - "Nez Perce Tribesmen of Columbia Plateau", 1955, 1962; 1 item. (Box 18, Folder 1073)
  - Nonirrigated Cropland in Eastern Washington, 1971; 2 items. (Box 18, Folder 1074)
  - Northeastern Washington Community Action Association Application for Demonstration Grant, 1968; 1 item. (Box 18, Folder 1075)
  - Organizational Stages, Correspondence, Columbia Plateau Resources Council, 1966; 45 items. (Box 18, Folder 1076)
  - Pacific Northwest Conservation Program, 1969; 1 item. (Box 18, Folder 1077)
  - Pacific Region Photography Techniques, 1951-1970; 5 items. (Box 18, Folder 1078)
  - "Palouse Photographs Go Back to the Land", 1979, 1982; 3 items. (Box 18, Folder 1079)
  - Personal Lists and Maps, 1974; 22 items. (Box 18, Folder 1080)
  - Pine Creek Soil Conservation District Program, Washington; Master Plan for Soil and Water Conservation, 1951; 8 items. (Box 18, Folder 1081)
  - Pioneers of Farmington, undated; 1 item. (Box 18, Folder 1082)
  - Pioneer Stories, 1971; 12 items. (Box 18, Folder 1083)